<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cloud on ringoc&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://www.ringoc.com/categories/cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cloud on ringoc&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>ringoc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 11:55:28 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ringoc.com/categories/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Enable Redhat Golden Image BYOS in Azure</title>
      <link>https://www.ringoc.com/posts/enable-redhat-golden-image-byos-azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 11:55:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ringoc.com/posts/enable-redhat-golden-image-byos-azure/</guid>
      <description>What is this document? This document provides step by step instruction to enable Red Hat Golden Image with Bring-your-own-subscription (BYOS) in Azure by registering a Red Hat developer account.
Create a Red Hat Account If you don&#39;t have a Red Hat account yet, go to Red Hat portal and register an account. You can use either MSFT corporate or personal. (It is recommended to use MSFT corporate account so that any other RHEL for Service Provider On Demand can be grouped into single place/account)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Bastion on Demand</title>
      <link>https://www.ringoc.com/posts/azure-bastion-on-demand/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 23:30:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ringoc.com/posts/azure-bastion-on-demand/</guid>
      <description>Background Internet opens up tons of possibility, but at the same time your properties can become vulunaerable for security breach. It is important for everyone to maintain highest level of security for their properties.
In the Azure cloud environment, accessing your resources e.g. VM through SSH/RDP means you have to expose your port 22 or 3389 to the internet. One of the nice way is to use Azure Bastion.
What is Azure Bastion ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Terraform with remote TFE backend in Azure DevOps Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://www.ringoc.com/posts/terraform-with-remote-tfe-backend-in-azure-devops-pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 21:25:59 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ringoc.com/posts/terraform-with-remote-tfe-backend-in-azure-devops-pipeline/</guid>
      <description>Background Recently I worked in a project in large enterprise cloud migration project which using Azure DevOps Pipeline (YAML) as the core CD/CI pipeline which integrate Github repository as the source of truth, Terraform Enterprise workspace performing the IaC workload and Azure AD for IAM.
There are a number of benefits:
  Cloud-native approach with Terraform with massive number of providers
  Enjoy all benefits TFE offered e.g. collaboration, security, policy, and governance</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
